[DARKNESS] This is a wedding
between two nobles.
[DARKNESS]
You will be executed!
This is foolish!
You are so stupid to think--
I will not let
a dumbass call me stupid!
[KAZUMA]
What the hell is with you
trying to shoulder
all my debt like this?
[KAZUMA] It's like you wanna be
my wife or somethin'!
I thought I told you before!
If ya like me,
admit it already!
There is nothing
for me to admit!
You,
you are such a idiot!
[ALDARP]
You miserable peasant.
Lalatina owes me
a total of two billion eris!
Do you know what that means?
If you want her back,
that's how much
I expect you to pay.
[ALDARP] As if
such an outrageous sum
were even possible!
You just said it,
so no take backs!
[ALDARP]
What's all this about?
Here's the two billion
Darkness borrowed,
so now that you've got it,
we're outta here!
[shatters]
[coins clatters]
[all gasp]
[crowd clamoring]
Is that two billion eris?
All of those coins
belong to me!
Hey, don't you touch that!
[ALDARP]
No, stop! It's mine, dammit!
[ALDARP] Get away from there!
Each one of you! I'm serious!
What is this?
Where did it all come from?
[KAZUMA]
I sold out.
[gasps]
[KAZUMA]
Every single idea I had left,
and the rights to them too.
Also,
I added everything we've earned
from going on our quests
and it came out
to exactly two billion.
Seriously?
How could you?
You have got to be the most--
You don't get to say
"no" anymore! Understand?
[Kazuma grunts]
Listen up!
I'm gettin' my money's worth
outta you!
And you'll be earning back
every last coin with your body,
so you better brace yourself!
Do you get what I'm saying',
you degenerate Crusader?
Because if you do,
I wanna hear it!
[DARKNESS]
Yes!
[crying]
[gasps]
[thuds]
[KAZUMA] It looks like
I definitely landed
a critical hit
against her masochism.
[KAZUMA]
Man, does she have
the worst timing
with this stuff or what?
Get your hands off my...
[Kazuma running]
[Darkness panting]
You demanded
that I pay you with my body.
Now you carry me
like I'm your bride.
Hey do you mind?
Watch it with the drool!
[AQUA]
It's "Kazuma the Dirtbag."
Dirtbag?
[AQUA] He only returned
the money used to pay off
his own debt
but he's making it seem like
he bought Darkness.
What are you talking about?
I just meant she'd earn it
back as an adventurer!
[soldiers clamoring]
- Hey, Kazuma?
- Yo!
Run with your own legs, now!
[KAZUMA] All that muscle
is starting to get
pretty heavy, dammit!
I am not heavy!
[ALL]
Huh?
[DARKNESS]
I have had enough of this!
Lapdogs of the lord!
Time to step aside
and if you do not comply.
You are dead meat!
Come back!
You think rushing them
is gonna do anything?
Aqua I could really
use some buffs now!
Yeah, I've got you covered!
Are you ready for some
versatile entertainment?
[GUARD 1] Ow, ow, ow, ow,
ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
[ALDARP]
That's enough, men!
Never mind her!
[ALDARP] Get over here
and help me gather up my money!
[ALL] Sir!
Right away, Sir!
- Well played.
[GUARDS]
Lord Aldarp!
What do you people think
you're doing?
Turn around
and catch Lalatina, right now!
[KAZUMA]
All right!
We're almost clear!
[all gasp]
[Large Guard screams]
[thuds]
[rumbling]
[LARGE GUARD] You stop.
I no let escape.
[ALL]
So huge!
[guards clamoring]
Hey, they've got us trapped
we're surrounded!
[AQUA] So, what now?
What are we gonna do?
[YUNYUN]
Light of Saber!
[large guard groaning]
[Kazuma straining]
Huh?
[YUNYUN]
Megumin, I did it!
I actually did it!
[YUNYUN]
I-If my best friend asks me to
I-I'm even willing
to break the law
if that's what's necessary!
[MEGUMIN]
Yes, you are.
As expected of my best friend.
Huh?
The wizard you deem
wicked has arrived.
And based on instinct
I know I must now
kidnap the bride!
[electrifying]
[KAZUMA]
She's about to set off
Explosion magic
in the middle of town!
I know her!
She's a stark raving lunatic!
[NOBLE 1]
What's that light?
[NOBLE 1] Could it be
her Explosion magic?
Hey Megumin!
Do you see down there?
I think Kazuma already...
[gasps]
[chuckles softly]
It's obvious to me
she's bluffing!
That girl would never use
such a thing here!
I want them all
restrained at once!
Oh?
You're saying I would
think twice, is that it?
That I would flinch
at the thought
of using Explosion magic?
Well, I'm afraid
you're quite mistaken!
[MEGUMIN] So consider
the challenge accepted!
[ALL]
Huh?
Don't do it!
No, don't!
We're all staying back!
[NOBLE 2] Lord Aldarp, please!
Stop provoking the girl!
[KAZUMA] Just had
to steal the spotlight, huh?
I didn't expect
you to get here first.
[DARKNESS]
Megumin.
And Yunyun, as well.
Back at home...
I will have to thank you.
It's all right.
Because, after all
we are friends.
Y- You're such
a talented Crusader
so, I couldn't lose you
without a fight.
[Kazuma chuckles softly]
[ALDARP] All of you!
In the peanut gallery!
[ALDARP] I'm referring to those
who're obviously adventurers!
[ALL]
Huh?
My bride has been taken
and I want her back!
For a handsome reward,
of course!
[ALDARP]
Just name your price!
Are you listening to me?
[ALDARP] Soon, your days
of living hand-to-mouth
will be over!
[Kazuma gasps]
[crackling]
♪
[DUST]
Hey let's play some soccer!
Let's do this!
[SAKAMAKI]
Hey pass it here!
Get this game started guys!
[Bikini yawning]
[MAGE]
Going for the corner, huh?
[blows air]
[shook]
Ya see that?
They're all here
to help you get outta this.
So maybe you should flex
some of those brain muscles
and think about what you did.
[Darkness whimpers]
[chuckles]
[KAZUMA]
This story's pretty nice.
[TROOPS]
Lord Aldarp!
Ah!
You finally made it, I see!
Aw, crap!
We've gotta get going!
[MEGUMIN]
Kazuma!
[MEGUMIN] I can't.
I can't hold on much longer!
Can I release this thing, already?
I really need
to let it go please!
No wait not here, Megumin!
I can't hold it!
Hey you bet you can!
'Cause I know
you have it in you!
[KAZUMA]
Just hang in there, all right?
Don't tense up too much!
[KAZUMA] You've got this
and whatever you do
don't give up!
Here it comes!
[MEGUMIN]
Everybody get away from me!
[KAZUMA]
Run for it!
[MEGUMIN]
Explosion!
[explosion]
[explosions]
[people clamoring]
[glasses shatter]
[wind blowing]
[groaning]
[wand clatters]
This,
this is our chance to...
Huh?
Wow.
Are you actually hiding
behind the one person
you came here
to try and rescue?
Yeah, how awful.
[YUNYUN]
Kazuma, that's horrible!
[KAZUMA]
I'm Kazuma.
[gasps]
They're getting away!
[ALDARP] She can't use
Explosion magic again!
[ALDARP]
Restrain them!
Hey, Kazuma!
Kazuma! Wait up!
[crying]
Aqua?
[KEITH]
The pain!
Ugh, he knocked me right over!
My bone!
Dust, I really need help!
You've gotta save me!
[crying]
[ALL]
Huh?
Keith I'm here for you!
Lemme take a look at this.
His arm.
It's a comminuted fracture.
Enough of this farce!
Hey you!
You let go of me at once!
I thought that arm
was badly broken!
[DUST]
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
So you think you can put
my close friend in a wheelchair
without even offering him
a sincere apology?
You must think
you're hot stuff, huh?
[GUARD 1]
I thought he has a broken arm!
[GUARD 1] What's all this
about a wheelchair?
[GUARD 1]
I've had just enough of your...
Ow!
This bastard's
getting violent now!
You hear that?
The authorities
are going rogue!
They can't screw
with adventurers like this!
[ADVENTURER 1]
You won't get away with it!
Who do you think you are?
[thuds]
[DUST] After everything
the last noble put me through.
[DUST] I've got a whole lot
to take out on you clowns!
[KAZUMA] I guess I owe 'em
another round of drinks.
My beautiful bride!
Come back!
[ALDARP] Don't go!
Don't go, Lalatina!
[footsteps approaching]
Huh?
Wait you again?
[knocking on door]
[DARKNESS]
I'm coming in.
[door opens]
[all gasp]
[weak breaths]
[gasps]
[footsteps approaching]
[weak breaths]
You look quite lovely.
[IGNIS] And so much
like your dear mother.
I must apologize.
This wedding was all my idea
and it fell apart
in the worst possible way.
Did it, now?
[chuckles softly]
[IGNIS]
Kazuma.
I think I need to go
and get some fresh air.
[Kazuma sighs]
[IGNIS]
Thank you so much, my boy.
I'm grateful.
It was no big deal.
All I did was just pay back
what I owed her.
Kazuma.
I was wondering
if you would take my daughter
won't you please.
[gasps]
Thanks, but no thanks.
Couldn't take the punishment.
[Darkness screams]
You are unbelievable!
How could you
possibly say that?
[Darkness whimpering]
[KAZUMA] This guy's
one of the kingdom's pillars.
[KAZUMA] So,
he can see right through me.
[KAZUMA]
I understand.
And I'll take good care of her.
[sighs]
Lalatina,
do you enjoy
the life you have now?
Oh, yes.
For the sake of my friends,
I'm fully willing
to abandon everything else.
I see.
♪
[sobbing]
Thank you, Father.
All my life
you wanted the best for me,
and I love you.
When you start to feel better
maybe,
maybe we can talk
until I fall fast asleep.
About Mother,
the way we used to.
[chuckles]
It feels like
you're a child again, Lalatina.
Sweet girl.
Please stay here.
[DARKNESS]
Father!
[KAZUMA]
This is pretty rough.
He doesn't have much longer.
[AQUA]
All right!
Time for Sacred Break Spell!
[Ignis groaning]
[DARKNESS] Oh, no!
Father!
[Darkness screaming]
[Ignis screaming]
Your dad was cursed!
Mister you've just
gotta trust me, it was nasty!
But I used my power
and cleaned it all up
super nice!
[KAZUMA]
Huh?
[Darkness whimpers]
Everything should be okay!
Pretty awesome,
right, Darkness?
And Mister
you can talk about her mom
as long as she wants now!
[KAZUMA]
This story's pretty nice.
[ALDARP]
How dare you humiliate me!
You are such a worthless
waste of a demon!
That's all you can "adjust?"
[grunting]
[MAXWELL]
By some unknown means,
the curse on Sir Dustiness
seems to have been broken.
The curse is broken?
Unbelievable
and at this rate.
Look, Maxwell!
You need to warp this story
to suit my needs yet again,
you understand?
But I can't, Aldarp.
Oh, really?
You lowlife scoundrel.
[ALDARP] You were summoned
with this Divine Treasure.
[ALDARP]
Or did you forget?
Do it!
You aren't allowed
to refuse what I say!
I know.
But the powerful light
that broke the curse
is interfering.
[MAXWELL]
So, I can't.
You good-for-nothing miscreant!
[ALDARP] Enough of this!
Enough of you!
[ALDARP]
Here is your final order!
[ALDARP] You must bring
Lalatina to me right now!
[ALDARP] When you do,
I'll gladly pay your price!
You'll pay my price?
That's what I said!
Now stop wasting time or I--
[DARKNESS]
Your Lordship?
I have come to apologize.
[gasps]
This is excellent work,
Maxwell!
You have most certainly
earned your payment!
And you're released
from our contract!
[ALDARP]
Oh, Lalatina! Lalatina!
[MAXWELL]
The contract.
[door opens]
Oh.
Your Lordship.
Please, sir,
keep my friend safe.
- In exchange--
- I can have you all to myself!
You belong to me now!
[groans]
[Aldarp screams]
[VANIR] Did you really think
it was Lalatina?
[VANIR]
Well, that's too bad!
[VANIR] Because it was
none other than I!
[VANIR] Oh my. Such a massive
swell of negative emotion!
[VANIR]
How very flavorful.
This unmistakable
feeling of dread.
You must be the same as Max!
[MAXWELL] I'm sorry
but have we met before?
[VANIR]
I must've made
this introduction
thousands of times by now
but, I suppose
I can do it for you again.
[VANIR] Nice to meet you,
Maxwell the Warper of Truth.
[VANIR]
I'm Vanir.
[VANIR] The all-seeing.
A shrewd demon.
Vanir, huh?
Ah, yes!
I don't know why,
but that sounds
quite familiar to me.
[Vanir]
Let's go, Maxwell.
It's time you returned
home to hell.
You can't take him, yet!
He's my servant!
[VANIR]
Oh really?
[VANIR] You would dare
refer to one of my peers
and a fellow duke of Hell
as merely your "servant"?
A-A duke?
[VANIR] You should
consider yourself rather lucky.
[VANIR] If you'd
summoned any other demon,
you would've been
torn limb from limb.
[MAXWELL] Vanir!
Vanir!
[VANIR] You rose to your
station in life thanks to him.
[VANIR]
So, be grateful.
And, as promised,
you will kindly pay him
what's owed.
[VANIR]
The contract's over, as well.
You see.
I'm afraid the real issue,
as far as I'm concerned,
was the contract itself.
[Aldarp whimpers]
[Vanir]
I have to say,
you forced me
into playing a roundabout hand.
Wait a minute.
[VANIR] It is exactly
as you're imagining!
[VANIR] For I used
the truth behind the debt
as a pretense to inform the boy
and he became aware
of you and your schemes!
[VANIR]
Very good!
[VANIR] Your dark emotions
are magnificent!
[VANIR]
Sublimely flavorful!
This is madness!
What are you yapping about now?
[laughing]
[VANIR] All right, then.
I do believe we're done here.
[VANIR] I shall return
my comrade
then I'll go back
to working diligently
for that dimwitted entrepreneur.
[grins]
[MAXWELL]
Vanir, Vanir!
[MAXWELL] I need to take
my payment from Aldarp
before going back home.
Fine very well, then!
I'll pay your price,
now just get out of here and...
Oh.
[Aldarp screaming in pain]
[ALDARP]
Ow It hurts!
Yes, Aldarp!
[MAXWELL]
Wonderful screams, Aldarp!
[VANIR] The price asked of you
will be the negative emotions
that suit Maxwell's
distinctive tastes.
[VANIR] Of course,
with your remaining lifespan,
I doubt you'll survive.
[Aldarp crying]
[ALDARP] In that case...
[VANIR] You'd have someone else
from your family pay, I suppose?
[VANIR] Unfortunately,
that grand responsibility
is the contractor's alone.
[breathing shakily]
[VANIR]
So "no."
[VANIR] And though I'm sure
this feast is quite robust
anguish and despair have never
suited my discerning palette.
[Aldarp breathing] [VANIR] But
it's a special flavor
that Maxwell has grown
rather fond of.
[birds chirping]
Nobody can find Lord Aldarp?
Seems his long list
of wrongdoings
has come to light.
He sent the body-swapping
Divine Treasure
to princess Iris
as one example.
[DARKNESS]
And I hear he ran off
because he could no longer
conceal the truth.
No kidding.
Now, there is no need
to leave town.
[all sigh]
See everything turned out fine.
Yeah whatever.
Man, I'm tired from
spending' all night packing.
[MEGUMIN]
Well I suggest taking a nap
until later this evening
and then we can
have dinner at the guild.
Huh?
[KAZUMA]
What's up?
[MEGUMIN]
Are you okay?
[AQUA] Oh I guess you weren't
there for that, Megumin!
Ya see.
Kazuma literally
bought Darkness outright!
So, she's probably
too scared to come inside.
Whoa, I wouldn't
put it like that!
She's wrong, Megumin!
I mean, it's kinda true,
but that wasn't my intent!
[DARKNESS] I am so sorry
for how selfish I have been.
[ALL]
Huh?
And it was incredibly
foolish of me.
[gasps]
That's okay!
I don't mind one bit!
Though Kazuma ended up
footing quite a large bill,
I say, "all's well
that ends well!"
She's right!
Plus, we managed
to catch the curse
that was making
your father sick!
[all chuckle]
Most likely
all the money will be recovered
from Aldarp's seized assets.
But, still.
Huh?
[DARKNESS]
The intellectual rights
that you had to sell off.
[DARKNESS]
Those are gone, Kazuma.
[KAZUMA]
That's the problem?
Look, it's okay.
Maybe I'll open up a cart
and start cooking foh.
Hang on, I get my money back?
Yeah,
the two billion eris
you handed over
and any damages.
Two freaking billion?
There's something so special
about you, Kazuma!
Yeah,
it's that je ne sais quoi!
So, I was hoping to get
my little Emperor Zel
a fancy crib.
That Kazuma!
I agree, he's quite something!
By the way, I was hoping
I could get a new robe soon.
You're just a pair
of gold diggers!
But me,
my ass is gonna stay
at the inn for about a week!
[KAZUMA]
What's up?
[KAZUMA] We already said
we were good.
It is just
about the letter
I wrote the three of you.
[KAZUMA]
I get it.
[KAZUMA] To her,
it means she left our group.
[chuckles] Hey, is that all
you're worried about because I--
Are you kidding?
Don't be ridiculous!
As our Crusader, you are
a vital part of this line-up!
and we wouldn't
ever let you go!
That's right!
What are you
even talking about?
Are you playing
stupid or something?
[AQUA] There's only
one place you belong
and that's right here with us!
[KAZUMA] Aw, man!
What the hell?
[KAZUMA]
I was gonna say that, too!
W- Well, I uh.
[ALL]
Huh?
I am a...
I-I am a Crusader.
Though durable, my sword
skills are rather poor.
But...
[DARKNESS] If you are still
interested in considering it.
I was just wondering
if you would let me
join you again?
[KAZUMA]
Of course we will.
[gasps]
[Kazuma sighs]
Welcome home.
- Hm.
♪ Yes we are still going up ♪
[crying]
[DARKNESS]
I am home!
[KAZUMA] This started
when I lived with the princess
and turned into an existential
crisis for us all.
[KAZUMA]
Things got pretty busy
but before I knew it,
every day was fun again.
[KAZUMA]
I've got good friends.
Good acquaintances, too.
[KAZUMA]
So I'm gonna live in this town.
[KAZUMA] And when I start
itching for a little excitement
I'll set out on an adventure
with these guys.
[KAZUMA] Right here
in this wonderful world!
[AQUA] You almost what?
[MEGUMIN] You almost what?
What's the matter
with you, Kazuma?
Are you an idiot or something?
I thought the entire point
was to bring
Darkness back home to us!
H-He may have been in my bed,
but he only touched my stomach.
- In your bed?
Hey wait!
I mean, yeah, okay!
What's she's saying
is the truth
but she is the one
who put my hand there!
- Huh?
It is not like that!
I just thought, "If I am
marrying lord Aldarp then--"
She admitted it!
Darkness has confessed
to making
the first move with him!
I'll give you two some space.
Maybe I'll just take
Emperor Zel's egg
out for a little sunshine.
I guess I never realized
what a shameless woman
you actually are!
I feel so moronic
for worrying now!
Hold on!
Please you have
to wait a second, all right?
Hey, Kazuma!
[DARKNESS] You have
to help me explain this!
[KAZUMA]
If I have to.
Hey Aqua?
[KAZUMA]
I'm curious,
how does marriage
work in this country?
Now where did
that question come from?
Anyway, the first thing
you have to do
is turn in a notice of marriage
on the morning
of the wedding ceremony.
And then,
it's in the afternoon,
so, that means.
What brought this on?
Well, from what I've been told,
these types of things are
more and more
common these days.
[Darkness gasps]
[KAZUMA] She's a noble
who's a perverted masochist,
and a virgin
with an ex-husband.
If he left
in the middle of the night
then I think that means
you'd be considered
"abandoned," Darkness.
[Darkness sobs]
[Darkness sniffles]
Hey who cares
what all the forms say?
Divorceness.
[DARKNESS]
Do not call me Divorceness!